Hi, and that's awesome! I want to talk you about your hub-co-pilot plans.
The good news you can start using your hub-co-pilot for free
with some monthly limits on completions on chat interactions.
But if you want to use it for more extensive, you can use of course some higher plans.
And there go of this video to help you to choose the better plan for you
or understand that you don't need a plan you want to use it for free
or if you business or enterprise I can also
highlight some moments what plan is better for you.
So the first plan is a retire. It has some limited features.
It has a limit on quad completions about 2,000 completions per month.
It's when you type a code to do some suggestions for you
or do some suggestions in the chat interface
so it's everything counted. But I would say it's enough if you want to try it,
you want to test it. For example, in chat in EDU you can have
about 50 messages per month.
And of course not enough you want to work on an extensive project building
features but to do some bad projects it might be enough.
So it also allows you to use some models. It allows you to use
some popular and basic models. It's good for
porting good for some technical questions, phones, first for writing tests
but of course there are some more powerful models
which available in the higher plans. So it'll give you an access for
clouds on S3.5 for gaming need to 0.0 flash
for GPT for all GPT 4.1 and all 3 me.
As I told you as popular and basic models.
You can also use partially code review feature.
If you select your code changes in your IDE so it means you
do it locally and you can get some suggestions on what can be fixed or improved.
So the next plan is capital Pro. It has unlimited code
completions and access to some premium models
and the good news it includes a free 30 day tire for
some users who are new. It costs 10 dollars per month
or if you paid yearly. On your basis it will cost you
100 dollars and you can save 20 dollars.
So and of course if you're a student, if you a teacher or open source,
maintainer you can get it for free. I just need to find a specific form
and hit hard to compile it and just request the free access.
So as I told the code completions are unlimited.
The chart in IDE is also unlimited with included models
which we talk next. So you have all the models.
Like a pivot 3 suggests you you can also use additionally cloud
and that's 3.7 and that's 3.7 syncing and that for
all one or for me as I told you it's more powerful models which better for
complex tasks. And you can use fully the code review feature.
It's really relevant if you use it hub as a code base so you can do it
in pull request or you can also get compute request summaries.
So you can use hot hit hub cup pivot pro if you
code on daily basis if you're going to use it on daily basis for your
personal projects or for example if you work at company
some company's paid for hit hub cup pilot pro. So if you want to use it more
extensive this one is for you. For example hit hub cup pilot pro
hit unlock you advanced API models extend some request lemons and
add you few more extra capabilities. It costs about
$39 per month and $390 per year. Of course the prices are
updated up to date on on today. Yep it's might be if you will
watch this video in one year and two years it might be different. So that is
why I provided the link was the payment and plans page for hit hub
cup pilot in the resources so we can always visit it and
check if the prices are same but it will make you a good overview of
also what is better for you. It has all the models are
available in three and four prior but additionally you can use
Claude Opus 4 and GPT 4.5 or O3. It's the rest of the released models so you
can always get the fresh access to any model was released
recently and use it. It also has some additional features you can
exclude some particular files from cup pilot. For example if you work on a
big project and there are some personal information in these projects you
can exclude it so in for example free tire or
pro tire it might be more difficult to work with some personal
data you need to I know I remove it or don't don't send it to hit hub
and you can also have an access to audit logs so this plan is for you if
you want to be if you want to use a relatively published
models you want to use the old power of it hub the pilot. The next plan is for
businesses. It's for me it's for team organization. It's my
derivant for you if you are a team of two or three people
and you need to control an access you need to
have some short place. Yep. For example you're a big
organization like 250 people it's also can be great for you.
So the price is 19 dollars per month for every seat like
if you have three people you pay every people independently.
You can use models same as in hit hub cup pilot problem as I told you it's
powerful models which better for complex tasks here you can check them
this is all these models you can use. And about some additional features
you can have some organization policy management which will help you to
manage your seats and the people you have in your team.
As a cup pilot enterprise it's of course for big enterprise companies
which need more advanced features and some centralized management which is
better organized. It costs about 39 dollars per
every seat per month. You can use same models as for cup pilot problem
cup pilot problem plus one. You can check it here. It's additionally
close all those four GPT 4.5 some new models
was recently released. And you can use some additionally
coding guidelines for your code review so you can set up what is your
guidelines and how how an AI pilot should review your
merge requests. So you have more capabilities. You can also use
cup pilot knowledge basis to have a bigger context when
your developers work on projects. So I hope this
class over you will help you really understand and choose the better
plan for you. Of course if you just start you can start the physical pilot
pre-and-zance switch to any other plan as you want. So see you in the next